Memorabilia Collection, 1782-2011 (bulk 1866-1997): Finding Aid AC053
University Archives
- Series 14: Tobacco, 1870-1973; 18 boxes
  - Ash Tray, Undated; 1 box (Box A.35)
    University seal. Rectangular, orange with cigarette stand.
  - Ash Tray, 1939; 1 box (Box A.35)
    Forty fifth '94 Reunion. Black, round.
  - Ash Tray, 1966; 1 box (Box A.34)
    Pebble beach 1966. "See you in the West". White, round.
  - Ash Tray, Undated; 1 box (Box A.34)
    Nassau Hall. Wedgwood, white.
  - Ash Tray, 1902; 1 box (Box A.35)
    Class of 1877, 25th. Black with tiger.
  - Ash Tray, 1932; 1 box (Box A.35)
    Class of 1877, 55th Reunion. Black with U seal.
  - Ash Tray, 1879; 1 box (Box A.33)
    1879. Black cannon shape. Metal.
  - Cigarette case, 1907; 1 box (Box A.35)
    "Triennial 04 Reunion". Empty case of reunion cigarettes.
  - Cigarette case, Undated; 1 box (Box A.35)
    black. Seal on front.
    Given by William E. Curtis '29.
  - Cigarette pack, Undated; 1 box (Box A.35)
    "Princeton" Red and white design.
  - Cigarette pack, 1961; 1 box (Box A.34)
    AR.1998.020
    Reunions. 1916's 45th. Orange.
  - Class Day Pipe, 1898; 1 box (Box A.31)
    1898 white ceramic with bamboo stem.
  - Clay pipe, 1899; 1 box (Box A.31)
    Class of 1899. Bamboo shaft.
  - Clay pipe, 1897; 1 box (Box A.31)
    Class of 1897. Bamboo shaft.
  - Clay pipe, 1889; 1 box (Box A.31)
  - Clay pipe, 1891; 1 box (Box A.31)
    Class of 1891.
  - Clay pipe, 1892; 1 box (Box A.31)
  - Clay pipe, 1881; 1 box (Box A.31)
    Class of 1881.
  - Clay pipe, Undated; 1 box (Box A.31)
    "41-91". Painted orange and black.
  - Clay pipe, 1890; 1 box (Box A.31)
    1890. Painted orange and black.
  - Clay pipe, 1887; 1 box (Box A.31)
    1887. Painted orange.
  - Clay pipe, 1888; 1 box (Box A.31)
    1888.
  - Clay pipe, 1938; 1 box (Box A.30)
    1938 penciled on.
  - Clay pipe, 1877; 1 box (Box A.30)
    1877 class day pipes.
    Given by Mrs. John Stewart, daughter of John Howell Weatcott '77, on March 25, 1963.
  - Clay pipe, Undated; 1 box (Box A.30)
    Class day pipe. With orange and black ribbon, blue painted bowl.
  - Clay pipe, Undated; 1 box (Box A.30)
    Class day pipe. With string attached.
  - Clay pipe, 1899; 1 box (Box A.31)
    1899. Bamboo shaft, painted with shield.
    AR2000.052
  - Corn cob pipe, 1897; 1 box (Box A.30)
    Class of 1897. Long bowl.
  - Corn cob pipe, 1888; 1 box (Box A.30)
    Class of 1888.
  - Corn cob pipe, 1878; 1 box (Box A.30)
  - Corn cob pipe, 1878; 1 box (Box A.30)
    Class of 1878. Painted orange.
  - Gold cigarette case, circa 1928; 1 box (Box A.34)
    AR.2003.059
    Cover inscribed with initials "EBH;" inscription reads: "To Edward Blanchard Hodge from the Class of 1896\u2026"
  - Leather cigarette case, 1913 March 3; 1 box (Box A.35)
    "Reception and Smoker in Honor of W. Wilson, 1913" Tan with U seal. Given by Princeton Alumni Association of District of Columbia, March 3, 1913.
    EX4578
    Gift of Laurence C. Woods, Class of 1922.
  - Matchbook, Undated; 1 box (Box A.35)
    "HYP" H-Y-P Club of Pittsburgh.
  - Matchbook, 1967; 1 box (Box A.35)
    "32's 35th" White book with tiger.
  - Matchbook, 1969; 1 box (Box A.35)
    AR.1994.030
    "100th Anniversary 1869-1969 Intercollegiate Football" Princeton-Rutgers. Red and black book.
  - Matchbook, 1961; 1 box (Box A.34)
  - Matchbook, 1956; 1 box (Box A.34)
    Reunions. 1916's 40th. Orange.
  - Pipe bowl, Undated; 1 box (Box A.30)
    Corncob with "79."
  - Pipe holder, Undated; 1 box (Box A.33)
    Shaped like Palmer Stadium. Metal.
  - Princeton Ribbon, circa 1891-1900; 1 box (Box A.35)
    AR.1992.053
    Cigarette purchase souvenir. Orange ribbon with pennant. "Twelfth night cigarettes".
  - Silver and gold cigarette case, 1914 September 15; 1 box (Box A.34)
    Inscription "H.A.H.B. from P.R.P. 2nd September 15, 1914." Given to Hobey Baker by Percy R. Pyne.
  - Silver Cigarette Box, 1950; 1 box (Box A.45)
    AR.2002.007
    Gift to Radcliffe Heermance, Director of Admission 1909-1950.
  - Tobacco sign, Undated; 1 box (Box C.7)
    "Tiger chewing tobacco,"orange and black. 2'X1.5'
  - Tobacco urn, Undated; 1 box (Box A.32)
    Pipes and U seal design. Metal.
    AR1995.062
  - White clay pipe, Undated; 1 box (Box A.31)
  - Wooden pipe, 1934; 1 box (Box A.30)
    "P 1934"
  - Wooden pipe, 1923; 1 box (Box A.30)
    "P '23"
  - Wooden pipe, 1870; 1 box (Box A.30)
    "Spencer '70" Signatures of other members of 1870 class. Stem separated from bowl.
    Ex4533
    gift of JC Spencer '07.
  - Wooden pipe bowl, 1906; 1 box (Box A.30)
    "Thalna '06"
    EX5010
    Kienbusch.0gift.